siteharvest.com 2011-04-05

# Privacy Policy

## SKINDINAVIA, INC.

###### PRIVACY POLICY 

This privacy policy will advise you about how we protect your personal information and about what choices you have concerning our use of such information. Please read this policy carefully. We may need to change this policy from time to time in order to address new issues and reflect changes on our site. We will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose that information to anyone. Please refer back to this policy regularly. 

###### PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION

We may request personal identification information from you (such as your name, street address, telephone number, credit card number, e-mail address, and/or any other identifier that permits the physical or online contacting of you) in connection with your use of, or participation in this site. In all of these cases, we will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. Unless otherwise provided in this policy, this information is used for internal marketing purposes only. We do not sell, exchange, or release your personal information. Your personal information is not shared with any other third party or company outside of billing and shipping purposes. Additionally, we may contact those individuals who specifically request that we do so or in the event they have signed up to receive our products or services. 

###### NON-PERSONAL IDENTIFICATION INFORMATION

When you visit or download information from this site, our web servers may automatically collect web site usage information. Web site usage information is non-personally identifying information that describes how our visitors use this site. It can include the number and frequency of visitors to each web page and the length of their stays, browser type, referrer data that identifies the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting this site, and IP addresses. We also may determine your screen resolution and the technology available in order to serve you the most appropriate version of a web page, e-mail or similar service. 

###### COOKIES USAGE

We collect some anonymous information about how you use this site by setting and accessing cookies on your computer. These cookies track information such as how often you visit our site, what pages you view and where you go after you leave our site. The cookies track your computer, not you. They are not connected to any personal information about you.

###### LINKS

Users will find advertising or other content on our site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the contents or links that appear on these sites. In addition, these sites or services, including their contents and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policy (policies) at all. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any third party sites or services before providing any of them with your personal information. 

###### SECURITY

No data transmission over the internet or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

###### REMOVAL/CHANGE/OPT-OUT

You can send an email to: anna@skindinavia.com to request the removal or change of your information from our database or to no longer receive future communications.

###### CONSENT TO TRANSFER

This site is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada or elsewhere outside of the United States please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States. By using this site or providing us with your information, you consent to this transfer.

###### LEGAL PROTECTION

We may transfer and disclose information about our users, including personally identifiable information, and may use IP addresses to identify users in cooperation with internet service providers or law enforcement agencies, to comply with a legal obligation, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing this site and applicable laws, or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of this site, our users or others. 

###### PERSONS UNDER 18

If you are less than 18 years old, we require that you inform a legal or parental guardian of our Terms of Use and Privacy Policy before using this site or placing an order. 

###### SWEEPSTAKES/CONTESTS/PROMOTIONS

If you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest or other promotion (if any), your personally identifiable information may be disclosed to third parties in connection with the administration of such promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment and as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion. 

###### PUBLIC AREAS

Please review our restrictions on use and guidelines for user forums in the Terms of Use for this site. In addition, please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you may disclose publicly in user forums (such as message boards, online journals, or similar web pages). You are solely responsible for your public profile's content. We bear no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information that users may disclose in user forums or other public areas of this site. 

###### ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. Your continued use of the site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

###### CONTACT US

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our site or this Privacy Policy, please send an email to: [anna@skindinavia.com](mailto:anna@skindinavia.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question).

###### EFFECTIVE DATE

The effective date of this Privacy Policy is December 1, 2010.
